Hey guys, in this video I want to share
the seven reasons why the ketogenic diet
is the best for long-term health. If you
don't know anything about the ketogenic
diet, I put a link down below. You can
check it out. But here's the real
reason. When you actually get into
ketosis, which is fat burning, you're
running your body on a different fuel
source called ketones. You're no longer
running on just glucose. Ketones is a
superior fuel. It's the original fuel
that our bodies ran on long time ago.
And so we we do very well on it. It's a
clean fuel and it's uh very very
healthy. So number two, it produces the
most weight loss of any diet that I know
of. That's cool. Targeting the belly
primarily. Okay, so it will shrink the
belly. Um number three, it improves your
memory and your cognitive function. It's
awesome for kids that are um have
epilepsy. It's [clears throat] great for
if you have Alzheimer's,
Parkinson's. Number four, it improves
your mood, okay? So, your overall
emotional state, it'll actually help
that because when you're running your
body on the sugar, it you go highs and
lows. You get irritable, grouchy all the
time. So, you might want to get your
spouse on this diet. Okay. Number five,
rid cravings and hunger.
Yeah, I mean, how you going to actually
do a program on top of cravings and
hunger? It's insane for you to try to
diet when you have cravings or you're
hungry all the time. It's not going to
last. So, this will handle that because
when you're running your body on um
ketones, you don't have that fluctuation
in blood sugars. Number six, it improves
your metabolism. It actually can repair
a set point that is stuck at a certain
weight. It'll help allow you to bust
through that plateau
because you're fixing um this next thing
right here called insulin. So number
seven, it fixes the insulin dysfunction.
And this one is very, very powerful
because think about it, what does having
high insulin or insulin resistance or
diabetes turn into? You get strokes,
high blood pressure, polycystic ovarian
syndrome, a fatty liver, Alzheimer's,
I mean like uh aneurysms, all sorts of
terrible things happen to people um when
they have high levels of insulin. So, I
hope I'm selling you on this concept
that the ketogenic diet is the way to go
because it's a no-brainer. You should
try it and I don't think you'll actually
go back once you experience this. All
right, thanks for watching.